Now for the big quiz. In all seriousness, this is the most
complicated exercise I've given you so far this lesson. I want you
to implement the details view using the cursor loader and multiple text view
widgets. And I've got some hints for you. Use loaders
not adapters. What does this mean? Well, it makes sense. Your detail
view does not contain a list so you don't
need to use an adapter, but you can still
use the loader pattern. The loader pattern will automatically
observe for changes in the URI with a CursorLoader. The
second thing you want to do is pass the date
into your intent. The date is the important thing to
the detail you need to have passed into it
to properly query the content provider. Now remember, you can
actually get the current location settings from the utility function. So
all you really need is the date. I hope that helps.